Guide to the Arden B. Schell Watergate Collection, 1972-1974
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Arden B. Schell Watergate collection
1972-1974
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Arden B. Schell
C0041
11 linear feet (22 boxes)
This collection contains documents assembled by House Judiciary Committee Assistant Counsel Arden Schell, relating to the investigation of the Watergate Affair (1972-1974). The materials include evidentiary statements, printed (GPO) publications detailing the House Committee on the Judiciary investigation of Watergate and resulting impeachment hearings, and other textual materials such as correspondence, notes, and transcripts.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Collection donated by Ms. Arden Schell in 1995.
Historical Information
The papers included in this collection consist primarily of "evidentiary statements" gathered by the House Judiciary Committee's Inquiry staff during its investigation of President Richard Nixon and the Watergate break-in and cover-up. The Inquiry staff was charged with collecting evidence that would be used by the Committee to determine whether or not Nixon should be impeached. The evidentiary statements derive from the Nixon Oval Office tape recordings as well as testimony and documents from key White House, FBI, and CIA personnel.
Arden B. Schell was an Assistant Counsel on the House Judiciary Committee.
Scope and Content
This collection contains documents assembled by House Judiciary Committee Assistant Counsel Arden Schell relating to the investigation of the Watergate Affair (1972-1974). The materials include evidentiary statements, printed (GPO) publications detailing the House Committee on the Judiciary investigation of Watergate and resulting impeachment hearings, and other textual materials such as correspondence, notes, and transcripts. In addition to the Watergate break in, the subjects covered in this collection include materials on the International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation, domestic surveillance, dairy price supports, abuse of the Internal Revenue Service, and the activities of the Special Prosecutors.
Arrangement
Organized by subject.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collection and Archives also holds material about Watergate in the, the, and the.
Index Terms
Persons:
Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994.
Corporate Names:
United States. Congress. House. Committee on the Judiciary.
Subjects:
Watergate Affair, 1972-1974.
Contents List
- Arden B. Schell Watergate collection, 1972-1974
  The folder information also contains the old box and folder numbers.
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    1.1 ("Gemstone" Operation; "Plumbers" Unit; "Political Enemies" Project; "Sedan Chair II" Operation); Alfred Baldwin; Bernard Barker; John "Jack" Caulfield; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP); John Dean; Democratic National Committee (DNC); Finance Committee to Re-elect the President; Virgilio Gonzalez; H.R. Haldeman; Sally Harmony; Howard E. Hunt; International Telephone and Telegraph (ITT); Richard Kleindienst; Fred Larue; Paul Leeper; George Gordon Liddy; Jeb Stuart Magruder; Eugenio Martinez; James McCord; George McGovern; John N. Mitchell; Edmund Muskie (US Senate); Richard M. Nixon (re-election campaign); Robert Reisner; Carl Shoffler; Hugh Sloan; Maurice Stans; Gordon Strachan; Frank Sturgis; Watergate Hotel
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (1.1 - 1.5), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    1.2
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (2.1), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    1.3
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (3.1 - 3.4), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    1.4
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (4.1 - 4.5), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    1.5
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (5.1 - 5.7), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    1.6
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (6.1 - 6.5), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    1.7
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (7.1 - 7.8), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    1.8
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (8.1 - 8.2), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1.9
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (9.1 - 9.7), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    1.10
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (10.1 - 10.2), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    1.11
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (11.1 - 11.4), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    1.12
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (12.1 - 12.2), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    1.13
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (13.1 - 13.2), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    1.14
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (14.1), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    1.15
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1, 15.1 - 15.5, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    16
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (16.1 - 16.3), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    1.17
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (17.1 - 17.3), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    1.18
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (18.1 - 18.4), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    1.19
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (19.1 - 19.3), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    1.20
  - Evidentiary Notebook 1 (20.1 - 20.8), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    1.21
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    1.22 ("Gemstone" Operation; Key Biscayne, Florida; "Sedan Chair II" Operation; White House tapes--18.5 minute gap); Bernard Barker; Robert Bennett; Burning Tree Country Club; Fred J. Buzhardt; Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Ken Clawson; Charles Colson; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP); Kenneth Dahlberg; J. Dialberto; John Dean; Democratic National Committee (DNC); John Ehrlichman; Fred Fielding; Virgilio Gonzalez; Patrick Gray; H.R. Haldeman; Joan Hall; Lawrence Higby; Houston Lawrence; Howard E. Hunt; Bruce A. Kehrli; John F. Kennedy; Richard Kleindienst; Fred Larue; Paul Leeper; George Gordon Liddy; Jeb Stuart Magruder; Jeb Stuart Magruder; Robert Mardian; Eugenio Martinez; James McCord; John Michell; Powell Moore; Richard M. Nixon (re-election campaign); Manuel Ogarrio; Henry Peterson; John Sirica; Hugh Sloan; Gordon Strachan; Frank Sturgis; Vernon Walters; Washington Post; Watergate Hotel; Rose Mary Woods; Ronald Ziegler
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (1.1 - 1.3), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    1.23
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (2.1 - 2.8), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    1.24
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (3.1 - 3.4), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    1.25
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (4.1 - 4.6), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    1.26
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (5.1 - 5.2), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    1.27
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (6.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    1.28
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (7.1 - 7.2), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    1.29
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (8.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    1.30
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (9.1 - 9.2), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    1.31
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (10.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    1.32
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (11.1 - 11.4), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    1.33
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (12.1 - 12.2), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    1.34
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (13.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    1.35
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (14.1 - 14.11), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    1.36
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (15.1 - 15.5), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    1.37
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (16.1 - 16.8), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    1.38
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (17.1 - 17.4), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    1.39
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (18.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    1.40
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (19.1 - 19.12), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    1.41
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 1 (20.1 - 20.2), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    1.42
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (21.1 - 21.3), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    1.43 John Dean; H.R. Haldeman; Gordon Strachan
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (22.1 - 22.3), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    1.44 Fred Larue; Robert Mardian; John N. Mitchell
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (23.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    1.45 Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Evelyn DePue; Howard E. Hunt; Rob Roy Ratcliff
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (24.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    1.46 (Bugging); Douglas Caddy; Democratic National Committee (DNC); Howard E. Hunt; James McCord; George McGovern; John N. Mitchell; Lawrence F. O'Brien; Washington Post
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (25.1 - 25.3), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    1.47 John N. Mitchell
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (26.1 - 26.3), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    1.48 Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); Patrick Gray
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (28.1 - 28.5), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    1.49 Charles Colson; John Dean; Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); Patrick Gray; Senate Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (29.1 - 29.7), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    1.50 Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); John Dean; Democratic National Committee (DNC); Daniel Ellsberg; Patrick Gray; H.R. Haldeman; John L. McClellan (US Senate); James McCord
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (30.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    1.51 (Bugging); Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); John N. Mitchell; Robert Ziegler
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (31.1 - 31.4), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    1.52 Richard M. Nixon (statement on Watergate)
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (32.1 - 32.8), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    1.53 Kenneth Dahlberg; John N. Mitchell; Hugh Sloan; Maurice Stans
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (33.1 - 33.8), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    1.54 (Bugging); Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Democratic National Committee (DNC); John Ehrlichman; Daniel Ellsberg; Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); Patrick Gray; Richard Helms; Vernon Walters
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (34.1 - 34.4), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    1.55 Patrick Gray; Vernon Walters
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (35.1 - 35.3), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    1.56 George Gordon Liddy; Maurice Stans
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (36.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    1.57
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (37.1 - 37.4), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    1.58 Richard Ben-Veniste; Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); Fred Fielding; Patrick Gray
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (38.1 - 38.4), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    1.59 John Ehrlichman; Vernon Walters
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (39.1 - 39.3), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    1.60 Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Manuel Ogarrio Daguerre; Kenneth Dahlberg; Patrick Gray
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 2 (40.1 - 40.8), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    1.61 Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Robert Cushman; John Ehrlichman; Patrick Gray; Richard Helms; Howard E. Hunt; Howard Osborn; Karl Wagner; Watergate Hotel
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    1.62 ("Plumbers" Unit); Address Books; E. Howard Hunt; Bernard Barker; Robert Barker; Fred J. Buzhardt; Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Kathleen Chenow; William Colby; Archibald Cox; Robert Cushman; Kenneth Dahlberg; John Dean; Democratic National Committee (DNC); John Ehrlichman; Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); Fred Fielding; Lewis Fielding; Finance Committee to Re-elect the President; Patrick Gray; Richard Helms; Howard E. Hunt; Richard Kleindienst; Egil Krogh; George Gordon Liddy; Clark MacGregor; Jeb Stuart Magruder; Eugenio Martinez; James McCord; John N. Mitchell; Lawrence F. O'Brien; Manuel Ogarrio; Kenneth Parkinson; Henry Peterson; James Schlessinger; Senate Committee on the Judiciary; Earl Silbert; Maurice Stans; Vernon Walters; Watergate Hotel; David Young
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (45.1 - 45.6), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    1.63
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (42.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    1.64
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (43.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    1.65
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (44.1 - 44.7), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    1.66
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (45.1 - 45.6), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    1.67
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (46.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    1.68
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (47.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    1.69
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (48.1 - 48.12), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    1.70
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (49.1 - 49.4), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    1.71
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (50.1 - 51.7), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    1.72
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (51.1 - 51.6), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    1.73
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (52.1 - 52.3), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    1.74
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (53.1 - 53.3), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    1.75
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (54.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    1.76
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (55.1 - 55.4), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    1.77
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (56.1 - 56.5), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    1.78
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (57.1), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    1.79
  - Evidentiary Notebook 2, Vol. 3 (58.1 - 58.4), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    1.80
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    1.81 ("Plumbers" Unit); Dita Beard; William O. Bittman; Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Dwight Chapin; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP) (payment of Watergate defendants); John Dean; Democratic National Committee (DNC); John Ehrlichman; Daniel Ellsberg; Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); Dorothy Hunt; Howard E. Hunt; International Telephone and Telegraph (ITT); Herbert Kalmbach; Richard Kleindienst; Fred Larue; George Gordon Liddy; Jeb Stuart Magruder; Robert Mardian; James McGovern; John N. Mitchell; Herbert Porter; Hugh Sloan; Maurice Stans; Anthony Ulasewicz; Vernon Walters; Washington National Airport; Watergate Hotel
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (1.1 - 1.2), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    1.82
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (2.1 - 2.3), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    1.83
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (3.1 - 3.2), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    1.84
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (4.1 - 4.3), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    1.85
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (5.1 - 5.4), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    1.86
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (6.1 - 6.5), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    1.87
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (7.1 - 7.5), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    1.88
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (8.1 - 8.2), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    1.89
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (9.1 - 9.3), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    1.90
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (10.1 - 10.2), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    1.91
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (11.1 - 11.6), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    1.92 Kenneth Dahlberg
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (12.1 - 12.2), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    1.93
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (13.1 - 13.2), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    1.94
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (14.1 - 14.3), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    1.95
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (15.1 - 15.3), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    1.96
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (16.1 - 16.3), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    1.97
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 1 (17.1 - 17.2), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    1.98
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (18.1 - 18.5), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    1.99
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    2.1 (Camp David, Maryland; Pentagon papers; "Plumbers" Unit) Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Dwight Chapin; Charles Colson; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP) (payment of Watergate defendants); John Dean; John Ehrlichman; Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); H.R. Haldeman; Richard Helms; Dorothy Hunt; Howard E. Hunt; Thomas Jones; Herbert Kalmbach; Egil Krogh; Fred Larue; George Gordon Liddy; Jeb Stuart Magruder; James McCord; John N. Mitchell; Northrup Corporation; Herbert Porter; Donald Segretti; Maurice Stans; Gordon Strachan; Anthony Ulasewicz; Washington National Airport; Watergate Hotel
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (19.1 - 19.5), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    2.2
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (20.1 - 20.5), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    2.3
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (21.1 - 21.2), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    2.4
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (22.1 - 22.6), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    2.5
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (23.1 - 23.5), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    2.6
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (24.1 - 24.3), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    2.7
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (25.1 - 25.6), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    2.8
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (26.1), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    2.9
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (27.1), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    2.10
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (28.1), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    2.11
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (29.1 - 29.5), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    2.12
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (30.1 - 30.2), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    2.13
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (31.1 - 31.4), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    2.14
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (32.1 - 32.3), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    2.15
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (33.1 - 33.9), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    2.16
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (34.1 - 34.6), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    2.17
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 2 (35.1 - 35.5), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    2.18
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 3, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    2.19 (Executive privilege; Rancho LaCosta, California; San Clemente, California; domestic surveillance; wiretapping); Howard Baker (US Senate); William O. Bittman; John "Jack" Caulfield; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP) (payment of Watergate defendants); John Dean; Cartha DeLoach; Ervin Committee; Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); H.R. Haldeman; Lawrence Higby; Howard E. Hunt; Jerry Jones; Herbert Kalmbach; Donald Kendall; Richard Kleindienst; Fred Larue; George Gordon Liddy; Jeb Stuart Magruder; Peter Maroulis; James McCord; John N. Mitchell; Richard Moore; Herbert Porter; Senate Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities; Hugh Sloan; Watergate defendants (sentencing)
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 3 (36.1 - 36.2), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    2.20
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 3 (37.1 - 37.3), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    2.21
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 3 (38.1), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    2.22
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 3 (39.1 - 39.6), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    2.23
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 3 (40.1), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    2.24
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 3 (41.1), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    2.25
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 3 (42.1 - 42.3), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    2.26
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 3 (43.1 - 43.6), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    2.27
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 3 (44.1 - 44.8), 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    2.28
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 3 (45.1 - 45.7), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    2.29
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 3 (46.1 - 46.6), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    2.30
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 3 (47.1), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    2.31
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    2.32 (Executive clemency); Fred J. Buzhardt; Charles Colson; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP); John Dean; James O. Estland (US Senate); John Ehrlichman; Daniel Ellsberg; Patrick Gray; H.R. Haldeman; Howard E. Hunt; Herbert Kalmbach; Richard Kleindienst; Egil Krogh; George Gordon Liddy; Jeb Stuart Magruder; John N. Mitchell; Richard Moore; Paul O'Brien; David Shapiro; Hugh Sloan; Maurice Stans; Gordon Strachan; Fred Thompson; Washington Post; Watergate Hotel; White House (involvement in Watergate); Ronald Ziegler
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (48.1), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    2.33
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (49.1 - 49.3), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    2.34
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (50.1), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    2.35
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (51.1 - 51.2), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    2.36
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (52.1 - 52.3), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    2.37
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (53.1 - 53.3), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    2.38
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (54.1 - 54.2), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    2.39
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (55.1 - 55.3), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    2.40
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (56.1), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    2.41
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (57.1 - 57.2), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    2.42
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (58.1), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    2.43
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (59.1 - 59.5), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    2.44
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (60.1), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    2.45
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (61.1 - 61.4), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    2.46
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (62.1 - 62.4), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    2.47
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (63.1 - 63.3), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    2.48
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 4 (64.1 - 64), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    2.49
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 5, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    2.50 William O. Bittman; Dwight Chapin; Charles Colson; John Dean; John Ehrlichman; Daniel Ellsberg; H.R. Haldeman; Howard E. Hunt; Egil Krogh; Fred Larue; Jeb Stuart Magruder; Manyon Millican; John N. Mitchell; Richard Moore; Sherman Unger; White House (involvement in Watergate)
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 5 (65.1 - 65.4), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    2.51
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 5 (66.1), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    2.52
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 5 (67.1), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    2.53
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 5 (68.1 - 68.3), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    2.54
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 5 (69.1 - 69.6), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    2.55
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 5 (70.1), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    2.56
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 5 (71.1 - 71.8), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    2.57
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 5 (71.1 - 71.2), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    2.58
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 5 (72.1), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    2.59
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 5 (73.4 - 73.11), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    2.60
  - Evidentiary Notebook 3, Vol. 5 (74.1 - 74.2), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    2.61
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    2.62 (Executive privilege; Camp David, Maryland; Key Biscayne, Florida) Howard Baker (US Senate); Charles Colson; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP); John Dean ("Dean Report"; Testimony); John Ehrlichman; Patrick Gray (confirmation hearings); H.R. Haldeman; Howard E. Hunt (clemency); Richard Kleindienst; George Gordon Liddy; Los Angeles Times; Jeb Stuart Magruder; James McCord; John N. Mitchell; Paul O'Brien; Senate Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities; John Sirica; Watergate Hotel; Ronald Ziegler
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1 (1.1), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    2.63
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1 (2.1 - 2.2), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    2.64
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1 (3.1 - 3.2), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    2.65
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1 (4.1 - 4.3), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    2.66